<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Rpt_Bld_Workshop.label>workshop</Rpt_Bld_Workshop.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_Workshop.description>A shared workshop of jigs, benches and good light. Colonists here simply work faster.</Rpt_Bld_Workshop.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_Granary.label>granary</Rpt_Bld_Granary.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_Granary.description>Storage pits, drying racks and proper field tools. Farmhands sow and harvest with far less waste.</Rpt_Bld_Granary.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_Clinic.label>clinic</Rpt_Bld_Clinic.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_Clinic.description>Clean rooms, boiled instruments and a place to rest. Doctors tend and operate with steadier hands.</Rpt_Bld_Clinic.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_School.label>academy</Rpt_Bld_School.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_School.description>A library of salvaged texts and a quiet study hall. Researchers make faster progress.</Rpt_Bld_School.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_Barracks.label>barracks</Rpt_Bld_Barracks.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_Barracks.description>A firing range and sparring yard with a drill schedule. Colonists shoot and fight with more discipline.</Rpt_Bld_Barracks.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_Market.label>marketplace</Rpt_Bld_Market.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_Market.description>Stalls, scales and a reputation for fair dealing. Trades struck here favor the colony.</Rpt_Bld_Market.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_Hall.label>assembly hall</Rpt_Bld_Hall.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_Hall.description>A warm common hall for meals, music and news. Life feels a little less like survival.</Rpt_Bld_Hall.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_Watchtower.label>watchtower</Rpt_Bld_Watchtower.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_Watchtower.description>Watch rotations and signal fires spot trouble early. Raiders arrive in thinner numbers.</Rpt_Bld_Watchtower.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_Inn.label>inn</Rpt_Bld_Inn.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_Inn.description>Good beds and better gossip. Envoys and gifts sent from this colony leave a stronger impression.</Rpt_Bld_Inn.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_Garage.label>caravan depot</Rpt_Bld_Garage.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_Garage.description>Tack rooms, spare wheels and packed rations. Caravans move noticeably faster.</Rpt_Bld_Garage.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_ShipWorkshop.label>ship workshop</Rpt_Bld_ShipWorkshop.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_ShipWorkshop.description>A machine shop bolted into the hull. Crew aboard the gravship work faster.</Rpt_Bld_ShipWorkshop.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_ShipClinic.label>sickbay</Rpt_Bld_ShipClinic.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_ShipClinic.description>A compact medical bay with everything within arm's reach. Shipboard doctors work with steadier hands.</Rpt_Bld_ShipClinic.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_EngineBay.label>engine bay</Rpt_Bld_EngineBay.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_EngineBay.description>Tuned injectors and a maintenance pit for the grav engine. Launches burn less fuel.</Rpt_Bld_EngineBay.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_CargoHold.label>cargo hold</Rpt_Bld_CargoHold.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_CargoHold.description>Netting, rails and clever stowage. The crew can haul far heavier loads.</Rpt_Bld_CargoHold.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_NavRoom.label>navigation room</Rpt_Bld_NavRoom.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_NavRoom.description>Charts, beacons and a steady hand on the stick. Rough landings become far less likely.</Rpt_Bld_NavRoom.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_CrewQuarters.label>crew quarters</Rpt_Bld_CrewQuarters.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_CrewQuarters.description>Proper bunks and a shared mess instead of bedrolls between crates. The crew rests better and grumbles less.</Rpt_Bld_CrewQuarters.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_ArmoryBay.label>armory bay</Rpt_Bld_ArmoryBay.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_ArmoryBay.description>Hardpoints, gun lockers and drilled boarding responses. Attackers think twice and come in thinner numbers.</Rpt_Bld_ArmoryBay.description>
  <Rpt_Bld_TradeAntenna.label>trade antenna</Rpt_Bld_TradeAntenna.label>
  <Rpt_Bld_TradeAntenna.description>A long-range dish tuned to merchant frequencies. Trades struck aboard favor the crew.</Rpt_Bld_TradeAntenna.description>
</LanguageData>
